<module>
	<rawname>endpointman</rawname>
	<repo>unsupported</repo>
	<name>OSS PBX End Point Manager</name>
	<version>14.0.0.2</version>
	<type>setup</type>
	<category>Settings</category>
	<license>GPLv3+</license>
	<licenselink>http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.txt</licenselink>
	<menuitems>
		<epm_devices sort="1" hidden="true">Device List</epm_devices>
		<epm_templates sort="2" hidden="true">Template Manager</epm_templates>
		<epm_config sort="3" hidden="true">Package Manager</epm_config>
		<epm_advanced sort="4" hidden="true">Advanced Settings</epm_advanced>
		<epm_placeholders sort="4" hidden="true">Config File Placeholders</epm_placeholders>
		<epm_oss sort="0">OSS Endpoint Manager</epm_oss>
	</menuitems>
	<description>
		OSS PBX End Point Manager is the free supported PBX Endpoint Manager for FreePBX.
		It is ***NOT*** supported by Schmoozecom. If you are looking for a supported endpoint manager please look into the Commercial Endpoint Manager by Schmoozecom, INC.
		The front end gui is hosted at: https://github.com/FreePBX/endpointman
		The backend configurator is hosted at: https://github.com/provisioner/Provisioner
		Pull Requests can be made to either of these and are encouraged.
	</description>
	<changelog>
		*14.0.0.2* Fix problems after merging 14.0.0.1
		*14.0.0.1* Initial release of fork from OSS EPM inlcuding right Navigation, Bootstrap Device View and OSS Information Page
		*13.0.7.18* Fix missing function numRows Fix DateTimeZone class init Use count() instead of broken numRow() function Fix selected in template editor dropdown Changed some Spanish words to English on non-locales files
		*13.0.7.17* Fix Save button in custom template page
		*13.0.7.16* Use PHP timezone as default timezone instead of static America/Los_Angeles
		*13.0.7.15* Remove spanish wordages
		*13.0.7.14* Fix totally broken random number generator, Fixes issue with variable in json
		*13.0.7.13* Fix issue if directory doesnt exist during download
		*13.0.7.12* pjsip_support: Add support for extensions using res_pjsip driver,, long name descriptions are truncated
		*13.0.7.11* Add delete_device_by_mac func, Update Bootstrap-select 1.11.2, fix bugs epm_config JS
		*13.0.7.10* Add new dialog loading..., continue upate...
		*13.0.7.9* Add bootstrap-select, continue updating Template Editor...
		*13.0.7.8* Fix bug multi sql query is not found. Continue updating Template Editor...
		*13.0.7.7* Update i18n-es, global config dialog save, load config for ajax....
		*13.0.7.6* Add new function  getActionBar all class, update style textbox, textare Template Editor....
		*13.0.7.5* Update CSS Plugin JQuery (Liquid Slider), Fix Bug RightNav, continue update...
		*13.0.7.4* Update Plugin JQuery (Liquid Slider), continue update...
		*13.0.7.3* Fix RightNav edit template, Continue to update...
		*13.0.7.2* Fix Bugs, Continue to update...
		*13.0.7.1* Continue to update...
		*13.0.7* Organize code, Fix Bug's, Update OSS Endpoint Template Manager
		*13.0.6.8* Fix Bug Package Version Firmware is null.
		*13.0.6.7* Cleanup bad javascript
		*13.0.6.6* Fix missing files issues
		*13.0.6.5* Remove array by reference
		*13.0.6.4* Fix bug, generate file list export brands through AJAX, delete code not required, organize files.
		*13.0.6.3* Fix bug, optimize code.
		*13.0.6.2* Bring back in better check onlines
		*13.0.6.1* Fix Package Manager Enable/Disable inverter value, some fix bug more.
		*13.0.6* End Fix OOS Advanced Setting
		*13.0.5.2* More Fix OOS Advanced Setting
		*13.0.5.1* More Fix OOS Advanced Setting
		*13.0.5* Missing updated file
		*13.0.4* Fixes online check, Updates from Community member Javier Pastor Garcia
		*13.0.3* Fixes check online
		*13.0.2* Missing updated file
		*13.0.1* Updates from Community member Javier Pastor Garcia
	</changelog>
	<depends>
		<version>14.0</version>
		<phpversion>5.3.0</phpversion>
	</depends>
	<supported>
		<version>14.0</version>
	</supported>
	<hooks>
		<framework namespace="FreePBX\Console\Command" class="Chown">
			<method namespace="FreePBX\modules" class="Endpointman" callingMethod="fwcChownFiles">chownFreepbx</method>
		</framework>
	</hooks>
</module>
